So let's get started with that course.
Ento vamos comear com esse curso.
But first I want to explain you how you can get the most out of this course.
Mas primeiro eu quero explicar como voc pode tirar o mximo proveito deste curso.
Obviously you watch the videos and I highly recommend that you all to code along right.
Obviamente, voc assiste os vdeos e recomendo que todos vocs sigam o cdigo  direita.
Decode yourself.
Decode-se.
This is how you learn the most.
assim que voc aprende mais.
Additionally check my source code.
Alm disso, verifique o meu cdigo fonte.
If you are encountering issues you can find it attached to the end of each module and also to a lot
apenas um pequeno erro de digitao e, se voc no executar minha fonte codifique e compare com o seu, voc
of lectures for all the module and I do provide the source code because sometimes it's just a tiny typo
no ser capaz de descobrir o que h de errado no seu cdigo e obter uma compreenso mais profunda do porqu deu errado.
and if you don't run my source code and compare it to yours you won't be able to find out what's wrong
Se voc est encontrando problemas, voc pode encontr-lo anexado ao final de cada mdulo e tambm a
in your code and get a deeper understanding of why it went wrong.
muitas palestras para todo o mdulo e eu forneo o cdigo-fonte, porque s vezes
Also consider D many hints and things.
Considere tambm D muitas sugestes e coisas.
I will teach you in the debugging section of this course.
Vou ensin-lo na seo de depurao deste curso.
There I will teach you how to handle re-act errors and how to react to them and fix them.
L, vou ensinar-lhe como lidar com erros de reao, e como reagir a eles e corrigi-los.
Definitely something you have to know how to do.
Definitivamente algo que voc tem que saber como fazer.
So use that knowledge you gain there to fix any issues you encounter.
Ento, use esse conhecimento que voc ganha l para corrigir todos os problemas que voc enfrenta.
Now if you're stuck and you can't find error ask in the Q and A section.
Agora, se voc est preso e no pode encontrar erro na seo Q e A.
My team and I are more than happy to help you there but that's important.
Minha equipe e eu estamos felizes em ajud-lo, mas isso  importante.
Don't just ask there.
No pergunte aqui.
Also answered there.
Tambm respondeu l.
I'm not saying this because I don't want to answer your questions.
No estou dizendo isso porque no quero responder s suas perguntas.
I will but if you answer you'll learn way more than if you ask.
Eu vou, mas se voc responder, voc aprender mais do que se voc perguntar.
Asking is so simple but answering is hard.
Pedir  to simples, mas responder  difcil.
And you can't go wrong there.
E voc no pode dar errado l.
Even if your answer is wrong no one is going to kill you.
Mesmo que sua resposta seja errada, ningum vai mat-lo.
Instead you're going to learn if people correct you and answering forces you to think about a problem
Em vez disso, voc vai aprender se as pessoas o corrigem e as respostas obrigam voc a pensar sobre um problema
and find a solution.
e a encontrar uma soluo.
If you really want to become a great re-act developer you have to solve problems and answering the Q
Se voc realmente quer se tornar um grande desenvolvedor de reao, voc deve resolver problemas e responder
and A section is a good way of practicing just that and finally practice practice practice.
a seo Q e A  uma boa maneira de praticar apenas isso e, finalmente, praticar prtica prtica.
It's as easy as that.
to fcil assim.
Even after you've finished this course you've got to practice the things you've learned.
Mesmo depois de terminar este curso, voc deve praticar as coisas que aprendeu.
You have to build your own demo projects set your own challenges Dudi exercises from this course alter
Voc tem que construir seus prprios projetos de demonstrao definir seus prprios desafios Dudi exerccios deste curso alterar
the code you'll learn in this course practice react.
o cdigo que voc aprender neste curso prtica reagem.
If you follow these steps and follow through this entire course you'll be an awesome re-act developer
Se voc seguir estas etapas e seguir esse curso inteiro, voc ser um incrvel desenvolvedor de reaes
and you'll be able to apply for chops.
e voc poder candidatar-se a escolhas.
Become a re-act freelancer whatever you want with dad.
Torne-se um re-atuador independente o que quiser com o pai.
Let's dive into react and learn how it works.
Vamos mergulhar em reagir e aprender como funciona.